<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Shuttle Tracker</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Shuttle Tracker</string>
    <string name="GPS_bus">redbus.png</string>
    <string name="crowdsourced_bus">greenbus.png</string>
    <string name="colorblind_GPS_bus">cbredbus.png</string>
    <string name="colorblind_crowdsourced_bus">cbgreenbus.png</string>
    <string name="info_page">
        Shuttle Tracker shows you the real-time locations of the RPI campus shuttles,
        powered by crowd-sourced location data.

        \n\nSchedule
        \nMonday through Friday: 7:00 AM to 11:45 PM
        \nSaturday: 9:00 AM to 11:45 PM
        \nSunday: 9:00 AM to 8:00 PM

        \n\nInstructions
        \nThe map is automatically refreshed every 5 seconds.
        Green buses have high-quality location data,
        and red buses have low-quality location data. In colorblind mode, the green buses
        are replaced by buses with an aqua target/scope icon, and the red buses are replaced by
        a purple dial icon. When boarding a bus, tap \"Board Bus\", and when getting off,
        tap \"Leave Bus\". You must be within 20 meters of a stop to board a bus.

        \n\nPrivacy
        \nShuttle Tracker sends your location data to our server only when you tap \"Board Bus\"
        and stops sending these data when you tap \"Leave Bus\".
        Your location data are associated with an anonymous,
        random identifier that rotates every time you start a new shuttle trip.
        These data aren\'t associated with your name,
        Google account, RCS ID, or any other identifying information.
        We continuously purge location data that are more than 30 seconds old from our server.
        We may retain resolved location data that are calculated
        using a combination of system and user-reported data indefinitely,
        but these resolved data don\'t correspond with any
        specific user-reported coordinates.\n\n\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="about_page">Shuttle tracker is developed by the Rensselaer Center for Open Source
        by your fellow RPI students. As an open source application, anyone can help develop the RPI Shuttle Tracker
        regardless of experience! Any contributions are welcome, as well as feedback for our current team.
        If you would like to view our source code, click the button below and open our GitHub page, and you can
        open an \"issue\" to leave feedback for us.</string>
    <string name="github_button_text">Click to access our GitHub Repository!</string>
    <string name="repo_url">https://github.com/wtg/Shuttle-Tracker-Android</string>
    <string name="version_url">https://shuttletracker.app/version</string>
    <string name="buses_url">https://shuttletracker.app/buses</string>
    <string name="bus_numbers_url">https://shuttletracker.app/buses/all</string>
    <string name="stops_url">https://shuttletracker.app/stops</string>
    <string name="routes_url">https://shuttletracker.app/routes</string>
    <string name="board_bus_button_text">Board Bus</string>
    <string name="leave_bus_button_text">Leave Bus</string>


</resources>